Will Jenkins (Murray Leinster) Papers
Will Jenkins (Murray Leinster) Papers
- Writings
  - Perfection [alternate title: Twelve forty-five p.m.] (Box 47)
  - Persian love story, Saturday Evening Post, 1946 (Box 47)
  - Pete Blade pulls a gun, Western Romances, 1931 (Box 47)
  - Pete Cannon rides his luck, Cowboy Stories, 1933 (Box 47)
  - The phantom trail, Top Notch, 1923 (Box 47)
  - Philosophie ephemerale, Snappy Stories, 1918 (Box 47)
  - The phony princess, Sweetheart Comic / Fawcett, comic strip with Abner Sundell (Box 47)
  - Pink ears, Black Mask, 1922 (Box 47)
  - Pipeline to Pluto, Astounding Stories, 1954? (Box 47)
  - Pirate of Zan, synopsis (Box 47)
  - Plague, Astounding Stories, 1944 (Box 47)
  - Plague on Kryder II, Analog, 1964; novella (Box 48)
  - Plague ship (Box 48)
  - Planet of sand, Famous Fantastic Mystery, 1948 (Box 48)
  - The planet of the small men, 1962; book; typescript draft and carbon (Box 48)
  - [The planet of the small men] Der planet der kleinen, Utopia Zukunfts Roman, Nr. 523, 1962; in German (Box 48)
  - The planets, Astounding Stories, 1946 (Box 48)
  - Pocket universe, Thrilling Wonder Stories, 1946 (Box 48)
  - Poems and epigrams, Snappy Stories, 1918 (Box 48)
  - Politics, Astounding Stories, 1932 (Box 48)
  - Porthole, Romance, 1928 (Box 48)
  - Porto Rico basketball story, Top Notch (Box 48)
  - Portrait of the artist as a young girl, American Magazine, 1937 (Box 49)
  - Portrait of a gentleman (Box 49)
  - Post war, Argosy, 1943 (Box 49)
  - The power, Astounding Stories, 1945; also published in Sidewise in Time (Shasta, 1950) (Box 49)
  - The power planet, Amazing Stories, 1931 (Box 49)
  - Prescription, article (Box 49)
  - Preview, Coronet, 1944? (Box 49)
  - Prince Roussopoff's gardener, 1939 (Box 49)
  - The professional touch in writing, article (Box 49)
  - Prologue, Smart Set, 1919? (Box 49)
  - Propagandist; A dog named Buck, Astounding Stories, 1947 (Box 49)
  - Prophecy, Amazing Magazine (Box 49)
  - Proxima Centauri, Astounding Stories, 1935; also published in Sidewise in Time (Shasta, 1950) (Box 49)
  - Psycho, Saturday Evening Post, 1961 (Box 49)
  - The Puritan, Snappy Stories, 1916 (Box 49)
  - The purple warning [alternate title: The purple hieroglyph], Snappy Stories, 1919; also published in Illustrated Detective Magazine; includes correspondence, printed material (Box 49)
  - Pygie, Esquire, 1939 (Box 49)
  - Quarantine world, Analog, 1966 (Box 50)
  - The queen's astrologer, Thrilling Wonder Stories, 1949 (Box 50)
  - The queen's peacock, Snappy Stories, 1919 (Box 50)
  - The quest of the golden lie, Argosy, 1937 (Box 50)
  - Rachel and the stranger, Movie Magazine (Box 50)
  - The racketeer ray, Astounding Stories, 1932 (Box 50)
  - The raid of Nusi, 1942 (Box 50)
  - The real thing, 1953; television script (Box 50)
  - The red badge of courage, Movie Magazine (Box 50)
  - Red cañon, Movie Magazine (Box 50)
  - The red dust, Argosy, 1920 (Box 50)
  - The red dust, Amazing Stories, 1927; also published in The Mad Planet (Box 50)
  - The redheaded herring, Follies, 1922 (Box 50)
  - The red stone, Top Notch, 1925 (Box 50)
  - Red wine for love, Today's Woman (Box 50)
  - Reck'n you're right, Argosy, 1922 (Box 50)
  - Regulations, Thrilling Wonder Stories, 1948 (Box 50)
  - Rescue, Saturday Evening Post, 1961 (Box 50)
  - Rim star, 1963; book synopsis, possibly a variant of Spaceman [alternate title: The other side of nowhere] (below); includes correspondence (Box 51)
  - River pride [alternate title: Grandma], Collier's, 1938 (Box 51)
  - Robot pirate, Fantasy & Science Fiction, 1960 (Box 51)
  - Rogue star, Avon, published in Twist in Time (Box 51)
  - The rollers, 1934; novelette (Box 51)
  - A romance of the snows, Love Stories, 1921 (Box 51)
  - The room upstairs, Movie Magazine (Box 51)
  - The rope, Movie Magazine (Box 51)
  - The rose o'Sharon, Triple X Western, 1924 (Box 51)
  - The runaway skyscraper, Argosy, 1919 (Box 51)
  - Routine, Astounding Stories, 1958 (Box 51)
  - Ruckus on the range (Box 51)
  - Run, racehorse, run, Argosy, 1930 (Box 51)
  - Sacrifice, Young's, 1917 (Box 51)
  - Sagebrush slings the bull, Short Stories, 1924 (Box 51)
  - The saint, Smart Set, 1916 (Box 51)
  - Sam, this is you, Galaxy, 1954; also published in Twists in Time (Avon, 1946) (Box 51)
  - Samson and Delilah, Movie Magazine (Box 51)
  - Sand, Movie Magazine (Box 51)
  - Sand doom, Astounding Stories, 1955; also published in Colonial Survey Stories (Gnome Press, 1957) and Planet Explorer (Avon, 1957) (Box 52)
  - The Saragossa, Ace High, 1922 (Box 52)
  - Satan's Chapel, 1934 (Box 52)
  - Save 'em! Save 'em! Fire!, Snappy Stories, 1921 (Box 52)
  - Scalps, Triple X Western, 1930; book; also published by Brewer and Warren (1930); 3 folders (Box 52)
  - Score even, This Week, 1942 (Box 52)
  - The scoundrel, Secrets, 1924 (Box 52)
  - The sculptured Pan, Snappy Stories, 1917 (Box 52)
  - The seagoing locomotive, Top Notch, 1924 (Box 52)
  - Sea tale (Box 52)
  - Search in the mist [alternate title: Machinery], Saturday Evening Post, 1950 (Box 52)
  - Second landing, Thrilling Wonder Stories, 1954-1955; short novel; includes correspondence (Box 53)
  - The second Mrs. Frayne, Toronto Star, 1954 (Box 53)
  - The secret of room 917 [alternate title: Hotel hermits], Life Stories, 1945 (Box 53)
  - Semiramis, Smart Set, 1917 (Box 53)
  - The sentimentalists, Galaxy, 1953 (Box 53)
  - Seven on a griddle [alternate title: Smart guy], This Week, 1942? (Box 53)
  - Seven temporary moons, Thrilling Wonder Stories, 1947 (Box 53)
  - Seven temporary moons, CBS, television script (Box 53)
  - The seventh bullet, Ace High, 1922 (Box 53)
  - The seventh bullet, Danger Trail, 1927 (Box 53)
  - Sharkmeat [alternate title: Oscar], Collier's, 1938 (Box 53)
  - Sharks, Danger Trail, 1926 (Box 53)
  - She didn't belong [alternate title: Teenage], Today's Woman (Box 53)
  - Shelter hut, Collier's, 1939; includes correspondence (Box 53)
  - The sheriff, Western Stories, 1922 (Box 53)
  - The sheriff deals in facts (Box 53)
  - The sheriff learns a lesson, Toronto Star-Journal (Box 53)
  - The sheriff sets a trap, Short Stories, 1925 (Box 53)
  - The sheriff was a runt, Short Stories, 1933 (Box 53)
  - The sheriff writes a letter, People's, 1923 (Box 53)
  - The ship was a robot, Thrilling Wonder Stories, 1953 (Box 53)
  - Short history of World War Three, Astounding Stories, 1957 (Box 53)
  - Short talks on story writing, 1930; article; includes correspondence (Box 53)
  - Show down (Box 53)
  - Side bet [alternate title: Life was a side bet], Collier's, 1937 (Box 53)
  - Sidewise in Time, Astounding Stories; Shasta, 1934; 1947,; 1950; includes correspondence; 3 folders (Box 54)
  - Silent room [alternate title: Politeness], This Week, 1938 (Box 54)
  - The silver menace, Thrill Book, 1919 (Box 54)
  - Sisters, Secrets (Box 54)
  - Six guns cross the border, West, 1928 (Box 54)
  - Skag with the queer head, Marvel Magazine, 1951 (Box 54)
  - The skipper, Collier's, 1935-1936; includes correspondence (Box 54)
  - The skipper knows best, Short Stories, 1928 (Box 54)
  - The slipper of Lizette, Snappy Stories, 1919 (Box 54)
  - Skit tree planet, Thrilling Wonder Stories, 1947; also published in The Aliens (Berkley Press, 1960) (Box 54)
  - The sleep gas, Argosy, 1932 (Box 54)
  - Small boy, Toronto Star Weekly, 1940 (Box 54)
  - Smart bird Hugin, Short Stories, 1938 (Box 54)
  - Smart trick, Detective Tales, 1941 (Box 54)
  - Smart trick, Standard Magazine (Box 54)
  - So long ago, Snappy Stories, 1919 (Box 55)
  - Somebody's son, West (Box 55)
  - Something about a trapeze [alternate title: Again tomorrow], This Week, 1949 (Box 55)
  - Something for Steve, American Magazine, 1945-1946; includes correspondence (Box 55)
  - Something new in crime, Detective Fiction Weekly, 1932 (Box 55)
  - Son of the Flying Y, Fawcett, 1950; book; 3 folders (Box 55)
  - Song for two hands, Country Gentleman, 1940 (Box 55)
  - Sonora was a jinx, Triple X Western, 1932 (Box 55)
  - Sonny, Short Stories, 1925 (Box 56)
  - S.O.S. from three worlds, Ace Books, book (Box 56)
  - S.O.S., R.S.V.P., Astounding Stories, 1943 (Box 56)
  - South American, Life Story (Box 56)
  - South American, Secrets (Box 56)
  - Space can, Thrilling Wonder Stories, 1948 (Box 56)
  - Space captain, Ace Books, 1965; 2 folders (Box 56)
  - Space gypsies, Avon, 1966; book (Box 56)
  - Space gypsies, Avon, 1966; book; 2 folders (Box 57)
  - Space platform, Shasta, Pocket Books, Belmont, 1953; 1965; 3 folders (Box 57)
  - Space tug, Shasta, Pocket Books, Belmont, 1953; 1965; 2 folders (Box 58)
  - Spaceman, Analog, 1963; also published in Other Side of Nowhere (Berkley, 1963); includes correspondence; 3 folders (Box 58)
  - Spaceman, Avon, 1964; book synopsis (Box 58)
  - Spies should start in kindergarten, This Week, 1942 (Box 59)
  - Spooks (Box 59)
  - Spur (Box 59)
  - The star puppy, Holland's Magazine, 1923 (Box 59)
  - Starting right, Today, 1930 (Box 59)
  - The stew in Mersa, Zest, 1926 (Box 59)
  - The stolen honeymoon, Love Stories, 1923 (Box 59)
  - The storm that had to be stopped, Argosy, 1929 (Box 59)
  - Storm wings, Air Trails, 1930 (Box 59)
  - The story of Monty Stratton, Movie Magazine (Box 59)
  - Story, no name, Story Book, 1917 (Box 59)
  - The story of Rod Cantrell, Startling Stories, 1949 (Box 59)
  - A story of the trade, 1929 (Box 59)
  - Story outline for Basil Rathbone script (Box 59)
  - The strange case of John Kingman, Astounding Science Stories, 1948; 1959-1963; includes correspondence (Box 59)
  - A strange document found, Snappy Stories, 1918 (Box 59)
  - The strange people, Weird Tales, 1928 (Box 59)
  - A stranger comes to town (Box 59)
  - Stranger in the Arctic, This Week, 1938 (Box 59)
  - The street of magnificent dreams, Argosy All-Story Weekly, 1922 (Box 59)
  - Strickly on the up and up, Sir (Box 59)
  - A strigtly [sic] personal angle (Box 59)
  - Stub passes through Malagua, Triple X Western, 1932 (Box 60)
  - Success in writing, Author and Journalist, 1936; article (Box 60)
  - A success story, Sir (Box 60)
  - Suliman-ben-Daoud, Snappy Stories, 1917 (Box 60)
  - Survival [alternate title: Castaway], Collier's, 1939 (Box 60)
  - Survival [alternate title: Castaway], NBC, 1947; radio script (Box 60)
  - Suspense, CBS, 1952; television script for episode "Night Drive" by Halstead Welles, written for tv from story by Jenkins; includes correspondence (Box 60)
  - Suspicion, Confession (Box 60)
  - Swamp flowers, Snappy Stories, 1919 (Box 60)
  - The swamp was upside down, Astounding Stories, 1956; also published in Colonial Survey Stories (Gnome Press, 1957) and Planet Explorer (Avon, 1957) (Box 60)
  - Sword and Mongols, Golden Fleece, 1939 (Box 60)
  - Sword of kings, Short Stories, 1927; book; 2 folders (Box 60)
  - Symbiosis, Collier's, 1947 (Box 60)
  - Sympathy / Little bird, Snappy Stories (Box 61)
  - The syncopated marriage, Smart Set, 1916 (Box 61)
  - The taint in her blood, Love Stories, 1922 (Box 61)
  - Tale of the sea, Esquire, 1939; 1941; includes correspondence (Box 61)
  - The tale of the widowed sea-serpent, Zest, 1926 (Box 61)
  - Talents Incorporated, Avon, 1962; book (Box 61)
  - Tank four, Elks Magazine, 1942 (Box 61)
  - Tanks, Astounding Stories, 1930 (Box 61)
  - The taxi murder no. 1, Black Bat, 1933 (Box 61)
  - Teetotal takes a drink (Box 61)
  - Teletype, Collier's, 1954 (Box 61)
  - The temptress, Love Stories, 1921 (Box 61)
  - Ten grand, Short Stories, 1933 (Box 61)
  - Terror, American Magazine, 1946; 1955-1965; includes correspondence (Box 61)
  - Terror from above [alternate title: Air war], Collier's, 1939 (Box 61)
  - That Calidad hold-up, Cowboy Stories, 1935 (Box 61)
  - That damn fool Pete, Triple X Western, 1932; novelette; includes correspondence (Box 62)
  - There's no accounting for girls, Snappy Stories, 1919 (Box 62)
  - They do not understand it, Smart Set, 1916 (Box 62)
  - They passed this way, Movie Magazine (Box 62)
  - Thief, People's, 1922 (Box 62)
  - Things pass by, Thrilling Wonder Stories, 1948 (Box 62)
  - Third planet, If, 1962 (Box 62)
  - This star shall be free [alternate title: Antarean experiment], Super Science, 1949; 1961; includes correspondence (Box 62)
  - This is a success story (Box 62)
  - Those at the top, 1961; television script; includes correspondence (Box 62)
  - A thousand below zero, Thrill Book, 1919 (Box 62)
  - A thousand fathom bluff, Top Notch, 1922 (Box 62)
  - The thousand yard bull, Top Notch, 1923 (Box 62)
  - Three o'clock (Box 62)
  - Th' tark, Fantasy & Science Fiction, 1956; also published in The Aliens (Berkley Press, 1960) (Box 62)
  - Tiger, Argosy, 1966 (Box 62)
  - Tight place, Astounding Stories, 1945 (Box 62)
  - Ti Julio of the guanacos, Collier's, 1937 (Box 62)
  - Tiki-Lui, the god, Country Gentleman, 1937 (Box 62)
  - Time to die [alternate title: Turn backwards, o time], Astounding Stories, 1947 (Box 62)
  - Time to die [alternate title: Turn backwards, o time], television script (Box 62)
  - Time of passing (Box 62)
  - Time tunnel, Pyramid Publications, 1964; book (Box 62)
  - Time tunnel, Pyramid Publications, 1964; 1967; includes correspondence, carbons, corrections, and first Time Tunnel story linked to television; 6 folders (Box 63)
  - Time tunnel, 1967; second Time Tunnel story linked to television; 4 folders (Box 64)
  - To make a robot brain, Astounding Stories, 1953; article (Box 64)
  - Tom, Dick and Harry, Secrets, 1922 (Box 64)
  - Tombstone (Box 64)
  - Torrero, Movie Magazine (Box 64)
  - A touch of spring, Snappy Stories, 1917 (Box 64)
  - Tradition, Complete Stories, 1936 (Box 64)
  - Tradition, Standard Magazine (Box 64)
  - Tragedy in the Waldorf, Detective Story Magazine, 1921 (Box 64)
  - The trail of blood, Danger Trail, 1926 (Box 64)
  - Treasure metals, 1953; article and film script prepared for Hamilton Watch Company; includes correspondence (Box 65)
  - Trog, Astounding Stories, 1944 (Box 65)
  - The trouble on the Bar Q, Danger Trail, 1934 (Box 65)
  - Trouble on the voyage, Short Stories, 1936 (Box 65)
  - Tuilagi, Danger Trail, 1927 (Box 65)
  - The twilight song, Love Stories, 1921 (Box 65)
  - Two flags west, Movie Magazine (Box 65)
  - Two in a boat [alternate title: Two thousand dollars], Collier's, 1935 (Box 65)
  - The U-boat, Argosy, 1919 (Box 65)
  - The ugly duckling, Lover's Lane Magazine, 1923 (Box 65)
  - Under Capricorn, Movie Magazine (Box 65)
  - Under Chitna's clouds [alternate title: East face], Collier's, 1939 (Box 65)
  - Under suspicion [alternate title: Ciudad Vieja], Life Story Magazine, 1944 (Box 65)
  - Understanding, Standard Magazine (Box 65)
  - Union Station, Movie Magazine (Box 65)
  - Untitled, Confession (Box 65)
  - Untitled, Galaxy (Box 65)
  - Useless (Box 65)
  - The vault, Black Mask, 1922 (Box 65)
  - Vengeance I [alternate title: Battle piece], Argosy, 1936; includes correspondence (Box 65)
  - Vengeance II, Short Stories, 1948 (Box 65)
  - Vengeance of the week, Midnight, 1923 (Box 65)
  - Verse (a la Alice], Snappy Stories, 1919 (Box 65)
  - A very good day, True Experience, 1924? (Box 65)
  - A very nice family, Liberty, 1937 (Box 65)
  - Victorian story, McLean's, page 1 missing (Box 65)
  - The village of the devil-devil drums, Everybody's (Box 66)
  - The village of Plenty Fella Hell, Short Stories, 1951; includes correspondence (Box 66)
  - Virginia's promise, Love Stories, 1921 (Box 66)
  - Vixen, Collier's, 1939 (Box 66)
  - The voice of the city, Telling Tales, 1923-1924; includes correspondence (Box 66)
  - The wabbler, Astounding Stories, 1942 (Box 66)
  - Wailing asteroid [alternate title: Fortress asteroid], Avon, 1960; working synopsis, original with correspondence; 2 folders (Box 66)
  - The wall that Cupid climbed, Love Stories, 1922 (Box 66)
  - The wallet, Black Mask, 1922 (Box 66)
  - Wanted, dead or alive, Triple X Western, book; Wright and Brown (Box 66)
  - Wanted, dead or alive, continued (Box 67)
  - The war goes on (Box 67)
  - The war of the purple gas, Argosy, 1963; original with corrections, carbon typescript; 2 folders (Box 67)
  - The war with the Gizmos, Gold Medal, 1958; book (Box 67)
  - The warehouse murders, Black Bat, 1934 (Box 67)
  - A warning to my husband, Secrets, 1924 (Box 67)
  - We are middle aged and fat, Smart Set, 1917 (Box 67)
  - We were in the smoking room, Smart Set, 1916 (Box 67)
  - The web, Good Housekeeping, 1941 (Box 67)
  - The wedding, True Experience, 1924? (Box 67)
  - Wells of Pildori [alternate title: Poisoned wells], Frontier, 1927 (Box 68)
  - West wind [alternate title: Symbiosis], Astounding Stories, 1948; Also Collier's (Box 68)
  - Western novelette (Box 68)
  - The wharf killer (Box 68)
  - When I die, Snappy Stories, 1916; poem plus epigrams (Box 68)
  - When it's pulp and when it's slick, Report to Writers, article (Box 68)
  - When the deathbird sings, Danger Trail, 1927?; fragment (Box 68)
  - When the lights come on, Snappy Stories, 1917 (Box 68)
  - When the smoke flew thick, Top Notch, 1923 (Box 68)
  - Where the fatheads belong, Detective Fiction Weekly, 1932 (Box 68)
  - Which story?, Author and Journalist (Box 68)
  - Whiplash, Movie Magazine (Box 68)
  - White man's burden [alternate title: White man], Collier's, 1937 (Box 68)
  - White man devil, Wide World Adventure Clayton Magazine, 1929 (Box 68)
  - White spot, Startling Stories, 1955; 1965; includes correspondence (Box 68)
  - Wild waters [alternate title: Flood], Collier's, 1935; includes correspondence (Box 68)
  - The wilderness, Philadelphia Inquirer Sunday Magazine (Box 68)
  - The wind, Country Gentleman, 1942 (Box 68)
  - The wine of Calo, Snappy Stories, 1918 (Box 68)
  - A wireless for the fangless one, Short Stories, 1924 (Box 68)
  - The witch ring, Argosy, 1951 (Box 68)
  - Without a moment's uneasiness, Science Fiction (Box 68)
  - Wom'n, Telling Tales, 1921 (Box 68)
  - The woman who sold herself, Young's, 1917 (Box 68)
  - Women were remarkable (Box 68)
  - Woman's work, Columbia Publications, 1956 (Box 69)
  - Wrath unchanged, Popular Publications, 1917 (Box 69)
  - The wreck of the Israel Holman, Thrill Book, 1919 (Box 69)
  - The wretchedness of Estefan, Snappy Stories, 1919 (Box 69)
  - W. S. S., Argosy All-Story Weekly, 1919 (Box 69)
  - You can't get away with it, Detective Story Magazine, 1917 (Box 69)
  - You never can tell about dynamite, Fighting Romances, 1925 (Box 69)
  - You see I am blind, Life Story (Box 69)
  - You woman, Snappy Stories, 1917 (Box 69)
  - Young men prideful, Argosy, 1939 (Box 69)
  - The young signor, Short Stories, 1940 (Box 69)
  - Youth, Satellite, 1953 (Box 69)
  - Yvonne, Today, 1930 (Box 69)
  - Unidentified book (Box 69)
  - Untitled book on writing (Box 69)
  - Untitled stories, miscellaneous (Box 70)
  - Untitled stories, incomplete (Box 70)
  - Story fragments, 2 folders (Box 70)
  - Story ideas (Box 70)
  - Synopses, miscellaneous (Box 70)
  - List of titles not in the collection (Box 70)
- Manuscripts of others
  - Amos 'n' Andy, 2 Feb 2945; radio show (Box 70)
  - Arthur, Eric / The oldster, 3 Oct 1951 (Box 70)
  - Arthur, Kay / The long view, 23 Oct 1951 (Box 70)
  - Bailey, Anne Howard / Image, 5 Feb 1952 (Box 70)
  - Bain, Leslie / The deserter, original typescript (Box 70)
  - Benz, Hamilton / Domenico, 4 Nov 1951 (Box 70)
  - Bercovici, Konrad / 10 yards of poetry, 12 Feb 1952 (Box 70)
  - Bloch, Robert / Almost human, 13 May 1950 (Box 71)
  - Bradbury, Ray / The screaming woman, 25 Nov 1948 (Box 71)
  - Can you top this?, 16 Mar 1949 (Box 71)
  - Dudley, William / It takes all kinds, 20 Dec 1951 (Box 71)
  - Dudley, William / Mr. Bemis takes a trip, 26 Feb 1952 (Box 71)
  - Du Maurier, Daphne / The loving spirit (Box 71)
  - Holman, Doris / Little girl lost, 2 Oct 1951 (Box 71)
  - Ingram, Gail / Time to kill, 28 May 1949 (Box 71)
  - Marks, Marjorie / The way to end, original typescript (Box 71)
  - Marris, Hobbe / Yesterday's magic, 29 Jan 1952 (Box 71)
  - Meadow, Herb and H. L. Fishel / All quiet at Silver Valley, original typescript (Box 71)
  - Morwood, William / One foot in the grave (Box 71)
  - O'Neill, Frank / The man in 308, 11 Mar 1952 (Box 71)
  - Papashvily, Helen / The hat from Hangtown, 19 Feb 1952 (Box 71)
  - Ross, Jerome / Airtight case, 29 Oct 1951 (Box 71)
  - St. Joseph, Ellis / The weird world, 21 Aug 1967 (Box 71)
  - Turley, Jack / The trap, 5 Sep 1967 (Box 71)
  - Wilson, Anthony / The crash, 30 Aug 1967 (Box 71)
- Ephemera
  - Programs, 1952; 1966 (Box 71)
- Science fiction publications
  - F & SF Book Company, 1964-1965; catalogs 73-79 (Summer 1964 to Fall 1965) (Box 71)
  - Fanscient, 1948-1949; no. 3 (Spring 1948), 4 (Summer 1948), 8 (Summer 1949); Sent to Rare Books for cataloging. Please refer to to locate this item.
  - Fantastic Worlds, 1953; vol. 1 no. 3 (Spring), vol. 2 no. 1 (Fall); Sent to Rare Books for cataloging. Please refer to to locate this item.
  - Fantasy Advertiser, 1950; vol. 4 no. 3 (Jul); Sent to Rare Books for cataloging. Please refer to to locate this item.
  - First Fandom, 1964; no. 11 (Apr); Sent to Rare Books for cataloging. Please refer to to locate this item.
  - Galactic Outpost, 1963-1964; vol. 1 no. 1, 2;; Sent to Rare Books for cataloging. Please refer to to locate this item.
  - Galactic Outpost, Special issues 1, 2; Sent to Rare Books for cataloging. Please refer to to locate this item.
  - Galactic Outpost Complete index to Ace Books, by Roger Alan Cox, Oct 1964; Sent to Rare Books for cataloging. Please refer to to locate this item.
  - Gridley Wave, 1964-1965; no. 14 (Jun 1964), 17 (May 1965), 18 (Aug 1965); Sent to Rare Books for cataloging. Please refer to to locate this item.
  - Grotesque, 1948; vol. 2 no. 2 (Jan); Sent to Rare Books for cataloging. Please refer to to locate this item.
  - Index to science fiction magazines, 1962; Sent to Rare Books for cataloging. Please refer to to locate this item.
  - JG-Argassy, 1963; no. 60 (Winter); Sent to Rare Books for cataloging. Please refer to to locate this item.
  - Mana, 1956-1957; no. 2 (Winter, 1965), 3 (Spring? 1957); Sent to Rare Books for cataloging. Please refer to to locate this item.
  - Masque, vol. 1 no. 5; Sent to Rare Books for cataloging. Please refer to to locate this item.
  - Mercenary, 1965; no. 1 (Spring); Sent to Rare Books for cataloging. Please refer to to locate this item.
  - Mirage, 1963-1964; vol. 1 no. 6 (Winter); Sent to Rare Books for cataloging. Please refer to to locate this item.
  - Operation Fantast, 1950-1951; vol. 1 no. 5 (Jun 1950), 10 (Autumn 1951); Sent to Rare Books for cataloging. Please refer to to locate this item.
  - Publications of the Institute of Twenty-First Century Studies, special series no. 134, 136; Sent to Rare Books for cataloging. Please refer to to locate this item.
  - Science Fantasy Review, 1949-1950; vol. 4 no. 17 (Winter); Sent to Rare Books for cataloging. Please refer to to locate this item.
  - Science Fiction Advertiser, 1952; vol. 5 no. 5 (Jan); Sent to Rare Books for cataloging. Please refer to to locate this item.
  - Science Fiction Critic, 1937; vol. 1 no. 8 (Mar); vol. 1 no. 9 (May); Sent to Rare Books for cataloging. Please refer to to locate this item.
  - Science Fiction Review, Sep 1963-Dec 1964; no. 1, 2, 9, 10, 11, 13, 14, 16, 17, 24, 32, 34, 35, and index to no's 1-31; Sent to Rare Books for cataloging. Please refer to to locate this item.
  - Scientification, 1937; vol. 1 no. 3 (Jun); Sent to Rare Books for cataloging. Please refer to to locate this item.
  - Space Magazine, 1949; vol. 1 no. 1 (Winter); Sent to Rare Books for cataloging. Please refer to to locate this item.
  - Titania, 1950; vol. 1 no. 1 (Spring) 2 copies; Sent to Rare Books for cataloging. Please refer to to locate this item.
  - Warhoon, 1962; 1964; no. 16 (Jul 1962); no. 20 (Aug 1964); Sent to Rare Books for cataloging. Please refer to to locate this item.